http://www.celebrationcinema.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This version was last updated on October, 29 2018INTRODUCTION  Welcome to our Privacy Policy for our websites, mobile application,
rewards program, and social media channels (“Website”) of Loeks
Theatres, Inc. d/b/a Celebration! Cinema and Studio C (“Studio C” or
“we” or “us”).We respect your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal
data. This Privacy Policy will inform you as to how we look after your
personal data when you visit our Website (regardless of where you visit
it from) and tell you about your privacy rights.By using our Website, you consent to the data practices described in
this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the data practices
described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Website.IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE ARETHE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOUHOW WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATAHOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATADISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATADATA SECURITYDATA RETENTIONYOUR RIGHTSCALIFORNIA RESIDENT’S PRIVACY RIGHTS IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE AREFounded in 1944 by John D. Loeks, Sr., Studio C is a movie theater
chain with headquarters in Grand Rapids, Michigan, USA. Our theatres
serve the cities and surrounding areas of Grand Rapids, Lansing,
Muskegon, Benton Harbor/St. Joseph, Portage/Kalamazoo, and Mount
Pleasant.Purpose of this Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy aims to give you information on how Studio C
collects and processes your personal data through your use of this
Website, including any data you may provide through this Website when
you sign up to our newsletter, or purchase a product or service.This Website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.It is important that you read this Privacy Policy together with any
other Privacy Policy or fair processing notice we may provide on
specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data
about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your
data. This Privacy Policy supplements the other policies and is not
intended to override them.Studio C’s Contact InformationOur contact details are:Nancy Hagan, Chief Financial Officernhagan@bystudioc.com2121 Celebration Dr. N.E. Grand Rapids, MIChanges to this Privacy Policy and Your Duty to Notify Us of Changes  We will notify you of any changes to this Privacy Policy. It is
important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and
current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during
your relationship with us.Third-Party LinksThis Website may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and
applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may
allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not
control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their
privacy statements. When you leave our Website, we encourage you to read
the Privacy Policy of every website you visit.THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOUPersonal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified.We or our service providers may collect, use, store and transfer
different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped
together follows:Identity Data includes first name, last name, username or similar identifier, job title, date of birth.Contact Data includes billing address, delivery address, email address and telephone numbers.Financial Data includes payment card details.Transaction Data includes details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased from us.Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP)
address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting
and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and
platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this
Website.Profile Data includes your username and password,
purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback
and survey responses.Usage Data includes information about how you use our Website, products and services.Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.HOW WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATAWe use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:Direct interactions. You may give us your personal
data by filling in forms or by corresponding with us by post, phone,
email or otherwise. This includes personal data you provide when you:apply for our products or services;create an account on our Website;subscribe to our service or publications;request marketing to be sent to you;conduct a survey; orgive us some feedback.Automated technologies or interactions. As you
interact with our Website, we may automatically collect data about your
equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data
by using cookies, and other similar technologies. Please see our cookie
policy for further details.Third-party sources. We may receive personal data about you from various third parties as set out below such as Google analytics.HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA  We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most
commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:
(a) where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or
have entered into with you; (b) where it is necessary for our
legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and
rights do not override those interests; (c) where we need to comply with
a legal or regulatory obligation. We use your data in the following
ways:To register you as a new guest;To process and deliver your order, manage payments, fees, and charges;Manage our relationship with you;To enable you to complete a survey;To administer and protect our Website;To deliver relevant Website content and advertisements to you;To use data analytics to improve our Website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences;To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you.Marketing and Outreach  We strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data
uses, particularly around marketing. You can manage the marketing and
outreach we provide to you by opting out, which is described in the
“Opting Out” section below.Opting OutYou can ask us to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by
replying to a marketing email with “unsubscribe” in the subject line or
by Contacting us at any time.Cookies We may place “cookies” on the browser of your computer. Cookies are
small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your
computer’s hard drive. Cookies may enhance the convenience and use of
the Website. For example, the information provided through cookies may
be used to recognize you as a previous user of the Website (so you do
not have to enter your personal information every time), offer
personalized information for your use, and otherwise facilitate your
experience using the Website. You may choose to decline cookies if your
browser permits, but doing so may affect your ability to access or use
certain features of the Website.Web BeaconsWe may also utilize web beacons on our Website. A “web beacon,” also
known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web
servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information
collected through cookies back to a web server. The information
collected through these automated means may include information that we
gather and store about your visit to, and use of, the Website, such as
your IP address, type of browser and operating system used, date and
time you access the Website, pages you visit, and, if you linked to the
Website from another website, the address of that website. This data
does not include Personal Information and is not treated as Personal
Information under this Privacy Policy, but it may include the IP address
of your device. We may link an IP address to information that is
personally identifiable.Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can disable
this function so that your browser will not accept cookies. Please be
aware that disabling this function may impact your use and enjoyment of
this Website.DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATAWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third
parties who assist us in operating our site, conducting our business,
or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential.  Those trusted third-party partners may:Provide you and members with various servicesProvide database maintenance and securityHelp us manage transactionsHelp us process and fulfill orders or requests We may also release your information when we believe release is
appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or
protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.DATA SECURITYWe have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your
personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an
unauthorized way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to
your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other
third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process
your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of
confidentiality.We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal
data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach
where we are legally required to do so.DATA RETENTIONWe will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to
fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of
satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we
consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the
potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your
personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and
whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the
applicable legal requirements.YOUR RIGHTSUnder certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data.Request access to your personal data.Request correction of your personal data.Request erasure of your personal data.Object to processing of your personal data.Request restriction of processing your personal data.Request transfer of your personal data.Right to withdraw consent to us processing your personal data.If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, or if you have a complaint please Contact us.
Studio C commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of
your personal information. Inquiries or complaints regarding the
processing of personal data should first be directed to Studio C at
[insert contact].CALIFORNIA RESIDENT’S PRIVACY RIGHTSBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions
to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of
our site may make any changes to their information at any time by
logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Account’ page.Studio C does not track its Users over time and across third-party
websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore or does not
respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals.
